

INTRO:

I'm a B.Sc mechanical engineering student at the Iran University of Science and Technology. I have a keen interest in renewable energy systems. I have some experience in 3D modelling, Drawing, Research and Development, Solar Energy Systems, Hydrogen Production, Waste Recycling Systems and Machine learning. I am highly motivated to learn new things and work hard with others. Additionally, I can share my knowledge to others.

EDUCATION:

Iran University of Science and Technology

Bachelor Degree of Mechanical Engineering

GPA: 3.80/4.00, Grade: 17.50/20.00

National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents

Diploma in Mathematics

GPA: 4.00/4.00, Grade: 19.76/20.00

SKILLS:

SOLIDWORKS:

3D modelling, Drawing, Drafting, Simulation, Motion Study

MATLAB:

Programming, Simulink, Machine learning (ANN Toolbox)

Ansys:

Turbomachinery, Fluent, Mechanical

Python:

Programming, Numpy, Pandas, Machine learning (Scikit learn, TensorFlow)

PVsyst:

PV Power Plant Simulation

PVSOL:

PV Power Plant Simulation

HOMER:

Renewable Energy system simulation

AutoCAD:

Drafting, Construction Drawing, Cutting plan

AVEVA PDMS:

Piping, Iso draft

EES:

Thermodynamic analysis

Microsoft Office:

Word, Excel, Project, Power point

Sidewinder:

Conveyor designing

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Design Engineer & Piping Engineer

TTS Group - Full Time 2023 - Present

3D modelling of Sari Waste Recycling and Separation, Conveyor Designing for Waste Separation, Piping Engineering for Waste-to-energy power plant of Sari, GD&T, Research and Development

Teacher Assistant

Iran University of Science and Technology - Part time 2022 - 2023
Fluid Mechanic I

Research Assistant

Iran University of Science and Technology - Part time 2022 - Present

Machine learning application for Hydrogen production with Solar energy (Under Submitted)

Intern

Moshanir Power Engineering Services Co - Part time 2021

Wind Power Generation and Wind Turbine

Intern

Manjil Green Power Generation Co - Part time 2020

Wind Power Generation and Wind Turbine

RESEARCHES:

Weather Forecasting with Machine Learning

Prediction of the next day Temperature and GHI for Tehran & Zahedan with Python

Hydrogen Production Simulation

Simulating PEM Electrolyzer with MATLAB

Quality Control for PV Power Plant

Forecasting the next day Quality of Power Generation for Sama Zahedan PV Power Plant with Python

PV Power Plant Simulation

Simulating Sama Zahedan PV Power Plant with PVsyst

CONTACT:



m www.linkedin.com/in/iliya-baktash-626066248



Baktashiliya@gmail.com

